[(68, 'Report Specification', ['The count of all approved units for this member by SA Type Code, SA Category Service Code, and SA ID.', 'The total of all approved amounts for this member by SA Type Code, SA Category Service Code, and SA ID.', 'The count of all used units for this member by SA Type Code, SA Category Service Code, and SA ID.', 'The total of all used amounts for this member by SA Type Code, SA Category Service Code, and SA ID.'])]
